It is with great honor
and pride that I bring
the new Texas Quadrant
a message of hope.
The ONIX program watches
will allow inmates an opportunity
to rejoin their fellow men
in our ever-changing world.
Controversy surrounding all planters'
methods.
Of forcing criminals to
eliminate other criminals in lieu
of prison sentence has been
met with strong persistence.
The state declined the global infrastructure,
but remaining in the population.
Because it's harder and there's got to be
a difference.
It's painful.
They are just joining an executioner.
First of them, the first of them,
that's why it's scary.
Well, there's always been a difference.
That's why there's always been a
difference.
That's
why there's always a difference.
Who's going to be the first one to talk?
Alpire!
Who's going to be the first one?
You are kneeling on hallowed grounds.
Your blood is going to join others who
thought that their silence was noble.
Alpire.
Eyes forward.
They're already dead.
Will you be the one?
Tell me about Alpire.
D-Day?
What is D-Day, huh?
What is D-Day?
You're fucking useless.
Wait, wait.
I'm running out of patience.
You have three seconds.
What is D-Day?
D-Day is the future.
And then to all the suffering of those who
are lost.
That's all I know.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Micro nanites are the future.
So much about the nano world remains a
mystery.
But imagine this.
Our entire population could fit into the
size of bottled water, the nano dynamic.
Delivering medicine to patients can be
more efficient and pain-free.
You could purify our drinking water.
Create a new wave of renewable clean
energy.
After the Second Civil War, this great
nation was faced with a great problem,
overcrowded and underfunded.
We took the prison system and reshaped it,
created a path back into society for
inmates, who took advantage of the ONIX
program.
This is my true calling.
Alpire's true purpose.
A gift of hope.
I see the spark.
Spread it like a world of fire.
Burn it in the dark.
Do you want to dance?
I could take a chance in the only world we
know.
This is the beginning of flying in the
end.
Tell me what you said.
Tell me where you want to go.
Oh, good.
That's good.
You were right.
Alpire intends on unwilling upgrades to
the Watchers in three days.
Yeah.
We should have said more criminals lose to
kill each other.
The hell with whoever gets caught in the
crossfire.
Yep.
Simon found them all.
Well, it's off the entire communications
wing.
And I won't be able to gain access.
Whatever Eon is drawing up, it's for his
eyes only.
So the quadrants
haven't fully given them
autonomy, which gives
us a window to shut it down.
You'll have shed slayer.
The Onyx program was the beginning.
I know Eon.
There's something else to play here.
The criminals are eliminating other
criminals.
That's the rub.
Alire, things aren't just going to fall
into your lap.
You actually have to get your hands dirty.
My hands are dirty.
What am I looking for?
The name of his precious micronanites.
Amanda.
Why would you use your mother's name?
That son of a bitch is taunting us.
Don't I look into it?
No, no, no, no.
Why would he use her name?
That's it.
You're out.
I said I'll handle it.
I'm not going to watch you fail her again.
I meant... I said
I'll look into it.
Shit.
He needs a journalist.
Shit, he needs a journalist.
Where is it?
I told you.
Let's try this again.
Where is it?
Oh my God.
You can do this all night, Cammy.
I know you finished it.
Now tell me where it is.
Please.
It's a possible replicate.
Now why don't you ask him, Cammy?
Ah, but a motivated man can accomplish
anything.
Tax him up.
I thought you were.
You're a motivated man, Cammy.
I've done everything that you ask.
You love to create my original Onyx watch.
I'm just asking for you to do it again.
Son, wasn't it?
No, no, please.
I'm talking about all of a sudden.
You really didn't finish your fish!
Oh.
Jungle.
Tomorrow.
We will round the lights, Cammy.
This is not my job, you know.
Well, if you don't do it, guess it's not
going to get done.
Oh, I love you, Aleira.
But that means I get to teach you to not
be a brat.
Can you help me?
Hey, what's your name?
Sven.
Don't move!
It's all right.
We'll give you that watch.
Don't know what I had to do.
Stop moving!
Hey.
Who told you?
I told you I was right before I chose him.
Sven.
Listen, I need to know how much time you
have.
You take off that watch.
You okay?
He wasn't a threat.
You broke under a house, had a gun to your
head.
How much more of a threat does he need to
be?
Those are old tech weapons.
They're smuggled in from the north east
hole district.
I'm not worried about the gun.
I don't want to know why they sent a kid.
It was never helping me before to kill me.
Don't always your focus, Illero.
That's what they want.
Just throw that body at Alpiers door and
be done with it.
It's Daxon.
I know it is.
He's dead.
I saw to do that myself.
He on was just using that boy to distract
you.
Son of a bitch killed my mother.
And he wanted me to know that he's still
out there.
This is me getting my hands dirty.
Well, they are listening to me.
You have to get to Eon before
he can launch D-Day, before
he can spread the Onyx program
to the other three quadrants.
Get as many as you can!
Lock it down!
On me!
D-Day, continue to make D-Day do.
You never considered a date with me.
I guess you don't like fun.
Never said I didn't like fun.
Maybe I didn't like you.
Maybe that's your loss.
I remember when they told me you were
coming to my detail, I was thinking,
this girl is so pretty.
What does she do?
Just miss the scenery.
Well,
she's what happens when they send a bee on
it ahead of us.
Keep my crowns saying clear, do you hear
me?
Yes, sir.
This area should be demilitarized.
Only thing needs to be behaved more than
the outlier.
It's a living number of outlier.
How do you see it, Lucas?
I don't know.
The position of these prisoners seem odd,
coordinated.
Oh.
All of them dead in seconds of each other.
What do we think of?
They're sending a message.
A message?
Those prisoners were highly skilled.
They were carrying out in the agenda.
Agenda?
Where are you going?
Larry?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
What is it?
Hey, I got multiple dead bodies all over
the place.
What do you see?
Conspiracy?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Those are old tech weapons.
They're untraceable.
They're going to random casualties.
Too clean.
What do you think?
We wasn't here.
We'd be picking over these bodies like
vultures.
That woman was a cop.
Who made an ex cop?
The way you want to slice it.
Al paritatani equals Al paris bodies.
That's the story everyone will run with.
You put a run around making accusations
about Al paris.
You usually go missing.
Just want to warn you.
Be careful.
That's all I'm saying.
Lock me out for the rest of the day.
Search the records.
You're not seriously considering going to
northeast over.
It's the only place that Al paris can't
protect you.
Where I can't protect you.
Alara.
Cara!
Hey, will you let me ask you for that
favor?
Hey.
I'll check you when you get back.
Hey, are y'all looking at me?
That's right.
That's y'all for you to run and ship up in
here.
Vader.
No Al.
I'm looking for someone.
Hit with the green backpack.
I see shit.
Al pig motherfucker.
Lock.
Let's not talk to him.
Did you know where to fuck you up?
I mean, you must be outside your goddamn
mind.
We skinned out a pie of motherfuckers
around here.
You see him?
Oh, he waiting there on his last strike.
You get that by joining the Hall of Fame
over here.
He's in a lot of trouble.
I want to help him.
Get y'all saved.
Smart bullets.
Silver nitrate and mercury-laced.
Make sure both boil.
And the inside.
Green backpack.
Oh, you mean cairn?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, heep.
My memories.
It's funny sometimes.
He, um, he went down there.
Don't worry.
No else?
It's a place full of dingy motherfuckers.
Kind of like the folks you work for.
No offense.
Go.
Yeah.
I don't know what you are, but you ain't
out by it.
Either way, you go to know where else.
I said you'd be dead next 10, 15 minutes
anywhere or so.
Y'all want to fucking help?
Huh?
Think fucking GIJ ain't over here.
Y'all want to go help me out?
Oh, fuck y'all.
Oh, I'm cutting everything off.
Why if I go?
Half rations for a month.
No more bad tub wine.
Fuck y'all.
Y'all want to stop y'all carrying your
fucking asses over there in New Texas.
See if they fucking take care of you.
Good for that motherfuckers.
It's blew up my good note.
You have to get out of New Texas.
Daxon's free.
You said that you would protect my father.
That no one gets out of Al-Pair's
detainment program.
Right, Noel?
Listen to me.
Daxon killed my father.
He shot up the entire south block.
Kieran, your dad was the best guy from the
underworld.
You look like shit, by the way.
Which is why we let him live.
Gave him protections.
Now that he's gone.
Baby, I'm going to need another reason to
keep up our arrangement.
Fuck you.
I'm out.
You came to me.
Bagging for a way to get to Eon,
the head of Al-Pair.
And tell me, Kieran, what did you think
would happen?
Hmm?
Such a sad, sad way.
Now, give me.
We'll be agreed to.
I knew you wouldn't let me down longer.
This square is a way our debts.
All of them.
I've done no well.
Byron, what type of girlfriend would I be
if I let you leave without a gaffit?
This is a private party invite only.
A-Z.
I just want to say kind.
You're Al-Pair.
Our drop isn't due yet.
I'm super glad.
You're dead.
Go check it out.
Looks like I underestimated you.
What are you talking about?
Put it on.
Put it on!
Okay, okay.
Your target's Eon Prescott.
Oh, crazy.
The micronan attack
like the virus, causing your
body to attack all of
your healthy white cells.
A programmable killing machine.
You kill Eon and I get control of his
network.
You wanted the man who destroyed your
family.
This is your chance.
Thirty-six hours.
Where's Kari?
This is me asking nicely.
What's his name?
Jacob, hey, you're all right, okay?
Keep the pressure right here.
You've been right here, okay?
Just really.
Her agent, member Delta.
Can't charge tenants if they don't exist.
Many people.
I'm not sure.
Do you count the roaches in your wall?
We have towns.
How?
I can get them the eighth inning.
Al-Pair is the reason that we're in this.
Who do you think forced them to abandon
their quadrants?
Hey, Jacob, can someone get me a med pack,
please?
This man died today.
This one is on you.
Now you can call it in.
The man who killed my mother was wearing
that watch.
Well, that's impossible because this
belongs to my father.
Hey, where can I find him?
You won't.
He's dead.
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
Look, I can help you.
Yeah, but you're going
to need to smarten up
real fast because we
don't have a lot of time.
Leon's planning on launching the D-Day
program in three days.
Well, that's a relief because I have to
kill him in two.
You have to kill him.
What are you talking about?
It's personal.
You're Al-Pair.
Why do you care?
It's personal.
Look, I do not have time for this.
You have to get off the streets.
I'm good.
You can find your own way out.
All right, thank you.
Oh, and you believe that whoever gave you
that watch is going to stop it just you?
I can help you take down Al-Pair.
Love me that watch goes off.
One less rush.
So we're friends now?
Hey!
You're straight!
Yeah.
My friend and I were just talking.
All right.
Isn't that right, friend?
If you want to help this people,
you need to come with me.
We need to figure out where they want you
to kill you.
If you were lying to me.
Then we're both dead.
Just me and my company's a lot of things,
but...
We're giving.
They are not.
Cheers.
Al-Pair sees you and recognizes you.
Give me the water.
Leon?
We need to talk.
Lucas.
I have schedules for a reason and meetings
for a purpose.
But if it is, we'll have to wait.
Al-Pair sees you and recognizes you.
You want Dee Day to happen?
I think it's time you make an exception.
Goddamnit, she knows.
You know I grew up in this district.
Not so far from here.
A scared little boy awaited by his door to
be killed, to be kidnapped.
The very hands that would feed me would
also rise up into this.
This is why I started Al-Pair and created
the Onyx program.
So the people could know the serenity that
I came to know.
See through each other's eyes.
That what really truly separates us.
It's merely circumstantial.
And so you see.
What can be such a
heinous act for some is truly
nothing more than a
beautiful bond on kinsmen.
Because we innately all understand the
most important things.
Our most desirable outcome.
Who is that?
Survival.
Now, what has them all uncovered?
A lyric smart.
So all the intel has thrown at her.
She's been able to piece it all together.
Why is this a problem?
Because she knows Daxon is alive.
And then she figures out who he is.
And what we did.
I have contingencies in place.
Leon.
You're a home, Lucas.
What about a Lara?
I put her in your department so you could
keep an eye on her.
And make sure that we maintain the
advantage.
Given that you have failed at this task.
You are no longer a valuable asset.
So you will do nothing.
Say nothing.
Secretary of Defense may not approve of
you a little.
They don't know what I know.
So you might want to reconsider what you
may define as a valuable asset.
You fucking touch me.
Think about it.
Amanda thought us the value in sacrifice.
So much about a person's life could be
measured in many ways.
They make you feel seen, feel heard,
recognized.
They want all the odds are stacked against
you.
Like our brothers and sisters in arms who
lost their lives.
With senseless acts of violence today
downtown.
She exemplified what it meant to wear that
police uniform.
And to serve our community.
This is for you, darling.
To Amanda.
Amanda.
Thank you for coming.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Oh, that's great.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you, man.
Once you have it.
Oh, Robert, you should keep it.
I wasn't asking.
Thank you.
She would have been out there today,
you know.
She saw it coming.
I mean, if we're in it, it's...
Alpier was going to become.
Oh, we're going to become.
You remember when her and Jessica,
they put on the...
Oh, Officer Brown shirt?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Amanda said...
She said, if Alpier wants to
take all the cops off the street,
let's start with the codes who
voted for the Onyx program.
Brown turned red as a radish.
She had some moxing in her, didn't she?
Yeah, I still wonder how they found her,
you know.
Just as we were about to bring it all
down.
I appreciate you coming to this.
Oh, yeah.
I'm serious.
It's been ten years.
Larry.
Probably speaks of her mother anymore.
Come on.
Can you believe her?
Look, I still have a hard time with any
address, these old things.
Hey.
You follow up on any of those leads I sent
you?
Of course I did, Robert.
Are you sure having a Lara on the inside
is the smarter play?
Let me ask you something.
Yeah.
Why'd you quit?
Hey, later, Carl.
I mean, you came to...
The anniversary of your man's murder,
you gave me your badge.
Talked about the old days.
It's time.
No matter what, Robert.
Everyone believed that we were the problem
long before Alpier used us.
And you either live by their rules or
you're nothing.
And what do you want to believe in an
aunt's lawyer?
They're right.
We have time.
We can still finish what she started.
Have you seen the images out of North East
Hall today?
I mean, the Target and ex-copsoya.
What do you think's gonna happen once
Alpier is in every quadrant of the country?
That won't happen.
Yeah, how do you plan on stopping it?
With blood on my fists.
See?
Amanda knew that going down this road
would lead to nothing good.
She wanted us to maintain our seat at the
table.
They got a bullet in the head.
I don't talk about my wife like you really
knew her.
Oh, come on, sorry.
She taught me.
Now, before she died, she came to me and
told me she was gonna leave you.
Get out of my house.
That you would never understand.
Never do it was necessary to ensure that
Alar didn't grow up this thunder.
You know, that night was
supposed to be our last mission
together, that she was gonna
take a layer and start over.
I gotta say it again.
And hey, you listen to her.
Stop the Alpire.
She'd still be alive today.
Don't get out of my house.
Hey, what's going on?
I was just leaving.
We have a situation.
Yes.
It's gonna be a murder.
It's got you cleaned up.
It must have been a hell of a party.
Nice.
I thought we agreed you would just get
their attention.
Relax.
They'll take the heat for the dead cops.
And we'll follow through with our
arrangement.
It does not look like an Alpire MO.
It's not.
It looks like somebody's gone wrong.
Byron has the watch.
And Eon?
Yeah, we'll finally wait to get it to him.
It's too much of a survivor not to.
Now, while you make sure that he does,
Eon's gonna pay for what he did to me.
To us.
Some skill I've never seen before.
And made you say there were?
Just the one.
Mason came up through the Sentry Division
of Alpire.
In order for them to extract what they
needed from my head to start their program.
They didn't just see the algorithm work on
another soldier.
Well, after he killed
his parents, they started
using his skills for
more high profile targets.
Lab quotes were so intrigued, they didn't
account for the aftermath.
Of scrambling somebody's brain.
Some say he was chosen to be an instrument
of death.
What does that make you?
Then write your code out of the Alpire
system.
Eliminating the algorithm that drives the
onyx program.
On Siandai is the program automatically
shut down and reboot.
Or reboot?
Every watch will seem new directives for
its potential owners.
Owners are willing and ready to comply
based on new codes.
Our codes.
Our orders.
So all we have to do is get a watch on
everyone and we take over the onyx program.
I hope you've done enough to get his
attention.
Now, that's for my war dogs.
Avenue request.
An amendment.
Marva bonus.
I'm listening.
The girl.
My sources tell me she's Sawyer Bennett's
daughter.
Man responsible for torturing you for ten
years on a leash.
And the guy who stole your entire life and
turned into an empire on the other.
Yeah.
Out of the party indeed.
Dachshund.
No restraints this time.
No one.
It's crazy when it all happened.
You're for the east hole district.
My mother was.
Until Cameron took me and taught me about
the underworld.
Cameron.
Is that your father?
Yeah, I saw me like that.
Look, no disrespect.
But I'm not one for digging in the past,
you know?
Nothing but ghosts.
Whoever gave you that lost me how to keep
it out of the system.
What does that mean?
It means if I try to remove it without the
code, then we'll lose the watch.
And you'll die in the process.
I need more time.
Time is that our luxury we have.
I agree.
We need to go to Alpire.
We need to kill Eon.
Propped and solved.
24 hours.
That watch unleashes the rest of the
micronanites and your body will shut down.
All right.
No, Elle.
Where is she?
She's a shadow runner.
She used to run dark webcoding for Alpire.
I did runs for her back in the day in the
underground.
I can find her solo if I have to.
You're a scab.
He's carried sharp, son.
We're wasting our time.
Scabs do what they have to do to survive.
Your father created the Onyx watches.
People don't choose their circumstances.
We all use the handward delt to harvest
some goddamn sun beneath the storm.
Whose storm are you referring to?
So you get a bad hand, suddenly it's
everybody else's fault.
My mother died, begging
for Alpire scraps in
the pit, the same
company that you work for.
This place exists because of your father's
creation.
Cameron lost his life making sure this
watch didn't get into the wrong age.
Hey, enough.
To figure it out myself.
For the record, I only came here because
Daxon never misses his target.
I maybe bought myself a couple hours.
Daxon.
He slaughtered those people downtown.
He killed Cameron because they didn't give
him this watch.
Not letting the watch out of my sight.
Is that a threat?
You sure it was him?
You saw him?
Yes.
Not Ian from the beginning.
He was going to help him change the world.
Hell, we all were.
But there was... He just felt
there was something off that night.
The entire thing was a blurb, so...
Where did you go now?
I'm going to fight you.
This is Daxon!
Ian, his words, his vision...
was the beginning of the Onyx program.
The man who was the first target.
Ian may not have pulled the trigger.
It marked my words.
That was Alpauer's plan.
Some of my mother was just collateral
damage.
Like you don't understand.
But she was capable of what she was
willing to do.
And you didn't know her at all.
No other... listen to me.
They're here!
Get out of here!
What?
You're already dead.
No sign of Sawyer.
House is clear.
Turn it down.
And bring me Sawyer's head!
Find him!
Don't tell me you're going easy on me.
Queen of D-4.
Point E-5.
Well, there goes my pawn.
Now, we're talking about global assertion
for the Onyx program.
Not just domestic.
I think the United States
government as well, would
then try to ask for a
bigger piece of the action.
That is, of course, unless you doubt the
success of the launch.
Benjamin, we have offers
from Russia and China,
all trending well over your
generous contributions.
Countries that are well aware of the
program's success and its potential.
Three trillion to D-Munchka.
Five trillion from Wang Zu.
Come on, that doesn't even make my dick
hard.
Even my wife does better.
If you really want to tickle my taint,
Eon, you better give me something to
prevent me from pulling a plug on your
little science experiment the next two days.
The Onyx program was more than a criminal
explorative tool.
It was a mechanism in subversion.
Our formula has produced us surprisingly
on foreseen defect.
And what is that?
That human beings are instinctually
murderers.
That there is a purposeful imbalance.
That exists in all of us, right?
So how does letting
criminals kill regular
civilians with impunity
tie into this little matter?
As of last night, our
prior watches are being
distributed throughout
every district in New Texas.
Y'all going inside?
Fuck yo, Patrick Sertan III.
Yeah, motherfucking, who are you?
Oh, wait.
Hey, man, look, I told a bitch, I put
the child support check in the mail, man.
Post office be tripping, man, you know?
Listen, the mailman actually will write
down the road from my house.
We go get the money right now,
have you got the time?
In line with the article 034 in conjunction
with the United States government.
Man, the war, war, man, stop.
Listen, I don't... I'm hired here by orders
you to serve under the Onyx program.
And are you wearing that shit?
Get your ass out the window, I told y'all
was handling this.
You kid.
I mean, you leave my family out of this,
yeah?
You make me have to bust your ass out here
in my good road.
Now, look, you can take your little Fitbit
back.
I ain't wearing this shit.
Failure to comply will put you in direct
violation of conscription laws and would
lead to an immediate expulsion of you and
your assets.
Assets?
Thank you for your cooperation.
Lucas McNary.
I don't have a schedule, is it?
Something go wrong with the main branch?
And I'm at Article 034, I'll prior sure
did.
I know the goddamn article.
What is this?
Welcome to the Onyx program, sir.
Must be some kind of mistake.
Let me call you.
Arturization is directed from the
touching.
Up to the orders, man.
Robert Langley?
Can I help you?
It reminds us of Article 034.
We hereby welcome you to the Onyx program.
I don't understand.
What?
Put the watch on.
There won't be any problems.
Why am I getting a watch?
I mean, look, I work at Trinity Inspire.
I handled...
Who are you?
Who else is getting a watch?
Everyone.
What do you mean, everyone?
The entire New Texas District will be
under the Onyx program.
Um... Yeah, okay.
I gotta get some things.
My wife, Jessica, she needs to be
prepared.
Your wife died.
Years ago.
Mr. Langley.
Cancer.
Yeah, right.
Situations got me
a little... The watch.
Robert.
Now.
Thank you.
For your cooperation.
Let's go.
Naturally, given yesterday's
events, I couldn't wait for
your approval, as that would
compromise our larger goal.
Yes, son of a bitch.
You launched D-Day without the authorization
of the United States government.
I can have you fucking buried for that
here.
No, Benjamin.
The President gave the go ahead long
before.
I have merely amused myself with
pandering.
The Onyx program is a folly.
It's a fraud.
It won't work.
It'll never work.
This is a nation of laws.
Take away people's free will.
You inject them with a virus?
Programmable it not.
It's not only immoral, Leon.
It's illegal.
We are allowing people to operate under the
same principles that have built our ideals.
This illusion of democracy will fall.
We will start with New Texas
and develop the Onyx program
in every part of what's
left of our civilized world.
All crimes big or small will fall under
one jurisdiction, one rule of law.
And after they have disassembled each
other, they will long for order,
for a structure, a structure that we will
control.
Congratulations, Benjamin.
You were the United
States government of just
purchased the end of all
self-proclaimed freedoms.
And only obedience, service shall remain.
You're insane.
The people will go down.
Yes.
And who do you think owns
the hospitals, the vaccines
for our Onyx viruses that
each watch possesses?
Where?
Or where will they turn as their world
comes tumbling down?
Night to F4.
Checkmate.
We'll see.
Good luck.
Oh, Benjamin.
Don't forget to pick up a watch on your
way out.
Don't find us down here.
You need to get to know Wells.
Oh.
He was right there.
Finally sees him.
He's a 15-year-old girl like him.
Brownie.
Instead of fighting back.
He said he killed him.
If he stayed, you want to die.
How could my father have trusted that man?
I used to use people from the pits to test
out their weapons.
Just how I saw one of these.
It's like someone from a comic,
you know.
He didn't put this right through my
mother's head.
But everyone just walked over her like it
was nothing.
She wasn't even there.
So I don't think that there's some grand
plan for us.
You just pound the pavement with our
knuckles.
So there's nothing but bone.
Let himself go.
Okay.
I can come and reground the part.
You manage.
Go.
I'm fine.
There's more answers.
In here?
Look, it's what happened.
You know what's crazy?
I had you put on my details so I can spy
on you.
Why are you wearing a watch?
Oh, this?
I don't know.
I think it matches my eyes.
Where's I already started, D-Day?
Yep.
Did you know that Eon built the Onyx
program off the mind of a killer?
A serial killer, Daxon.
I mean, it's kind of genius if you think
about it.
You have to stop him.
Can you help me?
Everyone's getting the watch alert.
That's his grand plan.
He wants everyone to kill each other.
Is he going to be Lucas?
You know, we've been watching you since
your mother died.
Eon wanted to see if he can get someone
like you to break.
What are you talking about?
I asked your dad why he never came after
Eon himself.
You should ask yourself.
Why would a father...
send his only daughter into a snake dead?
He text me.
And I made the call.
He's in.
It had to be done.
What did she do?
All of it's a son.
All of it's in the position.
We didn't know that Eon would turn on us.
What did she do?
What did I do?
Alara, you murdered our pirates' tactics.
No, you don't.
Look at my bodies inside.
I'm going through their instructions.
Hey, hey, hey, careful.
They won't harm you.
They just want you.
What do you think?
I told you I could be fun.
Go.
Go now.
There's all grown up.
How'd
you know I wouldn't kill you?
I need the code to use the program,
the swatch.
Please, we aren't meant to live like this.
I know you feel the same way in a while,
deep down.
Daxon never planned on using my codes.
Where is he going?
To the Trinity Spire.
A pirate's entire mainframe is centered
there.
And if Daxon gets access to the
mainframe...
No one will ever be able to replace his
psych signature from Alpire source codes.
His twisted mind will live in the Onyx
code forever.
There is another way.
I must admit, I am in trust to this.
These are cute.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Give everybody time or just let it settle
inside you.
If they could we keep
you something occupied by
your time while we are
taking the sights, right?
What did you do to me?
Listen to me.
You have six hours to find and eliminate
your target.
If you want that, I don't want that watch.
Haren's a slippery son of a bitch.
But I have faith in you.
Open that door.
Get up!
Need a shoot, dumbass.
G.I.J.
See they got you with this shit too,
huh?
First time getting jumped.
Brothers and sisters!
There comes a moment in history when the
books written before us become obsolete.
And everything moving forward is the
truth.
Look.
Gotta get you off the street.
Gotta find Karen.
You can't find no one in your condition.
Oh, hell.
It's all time as weapons as all we had in
the watchhouse.
Never load with another rounding.
Jabs the barrel.
Always keep acquainted down when you're
not shooting.
Never up.
Backfire, blow your hand off.
Say word.
Hey, whatever you're about to do,
better do it quick.
We're taking back our freedoms tonight.
Tonight is that moment.
We have a chance.
A chance or so, our pyre, that we will not
be controlled.
That we will not let criminals roam free
in our streets.
That we will not be ruled.
Tonight is your moment.
Save it.
That's the ground they have.
Hey, what are you doing?
Where's your target?
Stay on the discuss route.
We want all eyes pointed at this caravan.
No, no.
Take another trip through the city.
Sir, I strongly recommend that we follow
diplomatic protocol.
With Michelangelo not watch the unveiling
of the Sistine.
Galileo never placed his gaze upon the
stars.
Sir, if we continue forward, we will lose
our essence.
I am from the people, therefore I am.
I am the people.
This is our victory.
I will not watch it from some boardroom.
Why did you do it, Rob?
They had their eyes on you long before I
gave you up.
Here are Eons rat.
And a Lara.
Did you think about what that would mean
to her?
Of course I did.
Elpiers got their hands in everything.
And now everyone.
Why did you?
We have to kill Eon.
Daxon is a virus that will upload me to
Elpiers at me.
Get off of me.
What's going on?
It's a big explosion.
The system will reboot if I kill Eon.
Destroying Daxon's source code forever.
Damn!
You see that shit?
Go on.
I got your color.
But it said it!
Not killing you turned out to be my
greatest achievement.
I mean, look at you.
You want to get another chance?
Might be right.
And again.
Night is still young.
Seriously, in the back.
So we finally get to finish our dance.
I knew it was fake.
The first time I saw you at the house.
Both of us driven by the same goddamn
things.
Hate, revenge.
Found me something, Alara.
Would you do to get those gloves?
You know the night your mother died?
I could see it in your eyes.
You and I.
Wasn't the same.
Can't you feel it, Alara?
D-Day's already live.
So everything a man have fought for is
ruined.
Wasn't supposed to be like this.
He said he could help her.
My wife!
He said he could find a cure.
How do we shut it down?
How do we shut this down?
Okay, we can't stop it from here,
but we might be able to buy some time.
We haven't shut it down.
Drop the gun!
You know, I do have to thank you for
giving me a purpose.
A true artist is really recognized on the
side.
It's such a familiar sound, isn't it?
The sound of no one can mean to save you.
There are your most desperate moments.
So all stirring silence of justice.
That's what makes us who we are.
There is life and our re-existence.
Feel this.
All that time I spent hating you for
locking me up like a dog.
I didn't have a choice.
You were a murderer long before Eon,
but a watch on your wrist.
I was a survivor.
But hey, it's all water in the bridge,
right?
Because now everyone will know what it
feels like to be desperate.
Once this goes live, and then they all
realize that there is no hope,
no way out.
No future.
Then, then we'll see whose truth wins out.
Until then.
No.
I got it.
I got it tonight.
Before tonight you were just another
accident.
An inconceivable mistake or less but now.
Look.
Even you can kneel before the future and
kiss its eyes.
You killed my mother.
And I've honored her with a legacy.
Can't you see?
Shut it down.
Now, only you have the power to do that.
You came here to finish a job to take a
life that you're not.
I'll be really so different, you and I.
Kill me and believe someone you just met.
Believe that it would stop the Onyx
program from going forward.
Or take the antidote.
And join me.
Will you be the one to shape our path
forward?
That's actually my story.
The algorithm has shown me that we crave
structure.
This version of mankind is irredeemable.
Time to let it all fall.
You are proving to me that you are a
survivor like me.
You understand more than this world will
ever know.
Take my hand, son.
Time to change your destiny is now.
I'll make my own.